Mariela, please.
Leave us alone.
If it had happened to you,
you'd be angry too.
What's your real problem
with me and my daughter?
You two are the problem!
So we won't stop
until we get what is rightfully ours!
- [MARIELA GRUNTS]
- [PRECIOUS GASPS]
- [THWACKS]
- [MARIELA GRUNTS]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FIRE CRACKLING]
[COUGHING]
[FIRE EXTINGUISHER HISSING]
- Billy! Oliver!
- [BILLY] Auntie?
The house is on fire! Let's go!
- Come on!
- Go! Go!
Be careful. Move!
- Billy.
- [COUGHING]
Auntie? [PANTS]
Billy, hold on.
Here, here, Billy.
[PRECIOUS] Oliver! Oliver!
- Get out of here!
- [PRECIOUS] Hurry! Let's go!
Billy!
- [CEILING THUDS]
- [BILLY GASPS]
[BILLY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [ENRICO] Hold on! Move!
- [PRECIOUS COUGHS]
- Auntie Pres!
- Jordan!
Jordan, Billy's still inside!
[ENRICO COUGHS]
- [BILLY SOBBING]
- Billy!
Stay there!
- [JORDAN GRUNTS]
- [BILLY SOBBING]
Are you hurt?
Can you get up?
We're here! Sir, over here!
[JORDAN, BILLY COUGH]
Oliver! Oliver?
They're okay now. It's okay.
Billy.
We'll follow them.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
[SNIFFLES]
[SIREN WAILING]
[FIRE CRACKLING AGGRESSIVELY]
[BEA] Ma.
Where have you been?
[MARIELA] Our problem is over.
We've finally had our revenge
on the family
who took away your father.
And on your father as well.
- Ma'am.
- Good evening.
I'll just give you updates.
We're still looking for Mariela Mercado
and her daughter, Beatrice.
We will let you know
as soon as we have any leads.
We've also obtained CCTV footage.
We already sent it to you.
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks.
All right. Let's go.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
She kept on yelling.
She was yelling at me.
She said…
She said we took what's theirs.
Bea told me the exact same thing, Auntie.
Do you think…
Billy, do you think Bea is aware
of what her mom is doing?
They came for LoveList.
And now our house too.
Who are they going to ruin next,
Auntie Pres?
You? Oliver?
My father?
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
Your blood sugar's low.
Take this.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you.
Oliver, do you feel better?
Yes, Charm.
Thank you.
It's fine.
I'm sorry the condo is a bit small.
But we'll be fine here.
You're all welcome here.
Your dad too. He can stay here
once he's recovered.
Just let me know
when you need anything, okay?
I'm just going to prepare food.
- Billy.
- Hmm?
When are we going back to the hospital?
Auntie Pres will be looking after Dad.
And you should rest.
I don't want you to also get sick.
- Billy.
- Hmm?
I'm sorry.
I got weak because of the fire.
I wasn't able to help you.
If Bro Dude hadn't arrived…
Buddy.
- Here.
- Bro Dude!
I brought clothes for you.
- Thank you.
- That'll look good on you.
[JORDAN] Look.
[OLIVER] Ooh.
Thank you.
Uh, dude.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
If you want to talk about anything, just…
Okay.
Guys.
- Billy, let's eat.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Let's eat! Let's eat!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's eat!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
Authorities reported
no fatalities in the fire
that broke out at the home
of LoveList CEO Benilda Cariño.
Her father, Enrico Dominguez, however,
remains in a critical condition
after rescuing his son, Oliver Cariño,
and a woman identified
as Oliver's guardian,
Precious Amador.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Did you hear what your father did?
Acting like a savior!
He went into the fire
to rescue his illegitimate child
and his mistress!
What about us?
What has he done for us?
Nothing!
[REPORTER] CCTV footage revealed
a woman entering the property
shortly before the fire started.
Police have identified her
as Mariela Mercado.
Mercado is now being sought by the police
and is considered a person of interest
in the investigation.
Anyone with information
on her whereabouts
is urged to contact
local authorities immediately.
Why…
Why should I be punished?
[SOBBING] They're the ones
who should suffer!
Not me!
Not us!
They should've died in the fire!
They should all die!
[CRYING] I don't want to go to jail!
- [CRYING, SNIFFLING]
- Hush now.
You won't go to jail, Ma, okay?
You won't go to jail.
I'll find a way to get you out
of this. I'll protect you.
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep you out of jail, okay?
[MARIELA] You promise?
[CRYING CONTINUES]
Yes, Ma, I promise.
You won't go to jail.
I promise.
I promise, Ma.
- [CRYING CONTINUES]
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
Where's Charm?
You guys got this. Uh…
just eat, okay?
[UTENSIL CLANKS]
Presenting…
the Billy Fashion Show!
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Introducing our house clothes fashion!
You can sleep in it.
- [MUSIC TURNS UPBEAT]
- [FAKE SNORING]
And when a guest comes over…
Bam!
Slay!
[CHUCKLING, APPLAUSE]
And we have one for the market.
We have the "grocery fashion"!
- [YANI] There she is!
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
So elegant!
But of course,
it should still be comfortable.
Hmm, see?
- But if you spot a cutie pie…
- [SHRIEKS]
Bam!
You go, girl!
Ooh, she's a dancer!
And for the office,
we have the "girlboss fashion"!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
And of course,
so professional!
Clean,
lowkey,
and lowest.
[LAUGHTER]
See? Give it up for Toni!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
But when it's time to face investors,
Chief-Mode on!
- [CHEERS, APPLAUSE]
- [MOUTHING WORDS]
- I can buy you!
- Wow! [LAUGHS]
She can buy you all.
- Whoo!
- She can!
[CHEERS, APPLAUSE]
Thank you!
Cocktails for clients and advertisers?
We got you, Pikachu!
- We have my twin here!
- [MAN] Yeah!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
So sweet, so pretty, so sexy.
So me.
[CHUCKLES, GIGGLES]
But if you get bored,
we have…
[IMITATES DRUM ROLL]
- Okay!
- Jade & Jude's kind of drip!
[CHEERS, APPLAUSE]
Drip it, girl! Drip it, girl!
Lower! Lower! Lower!
- Drip it, girl! Lower!
- Go, Val!
Spot the difference. [CHUCKLES]
And last but not least,
we also went shopping
for Auntie Pres and got her…
- the Auntie fit!
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
Hello, Auntie Charm!
- See?
- Auntie Charm?
- Yes, "Auntie."
- Show your respect.
God bless you.
[APPLAUSE]
- Yeah!
- We got you, chief!
Did you like it?
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Thank you.
[BLAIRE GUSHES]
[BILLY] Thank you, guys.
[BLAIRE] You're most welcome.
You want a hug?
- Let's hug!
- Hug time!
[FRIENDS] Aw!
Group hug! Group hug!
- Yeah!
- [BILLY SNIFFLES]
[CHUCKLES]
We're here for you, Billy. Okay?
- I love you, Billy.
- We love you, chief.
- We love you, chief!
- We love you, Billy!
Wilfred?
You're Caloy's friend. Wilfred, right?
Uh… Didn't he help you
unlock your wife's phone?
Oh…
You're that chick Caloy likes.
I remember you.
Abi, right?
It's Bea now.
I came here because
I want to change my name again.
You need a fake passport?
For my mom and me.
Hmm…
Looks like you and your mom
are in trouble.
Where are you running off to?
Can you do it?
Absolutely.
Okay, how much?
Well, since Caloy likes you…
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
I'm his girlfriend, actually.
- We're together.
- [LAUGHS]
Too bad he's in jail. [CHUCKLES]
How much will it cost?
[CLICKS TEETH] Well…
You can definitely afford it.
- 600,000.
- 600,000?!
What?
Look.
Two passports will need
two birth certificates as well.
I'm not even going to ask
for a down payment.
This is a good deal.
If you don't want it, find someone else.
No, no, no. I'll pay 600,000.
- But are you sure you can do it?
- Absolutely.
- Okay. I'll take your word.
- Okay.
600,000 pesos?
Where am I going to get that much money?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Pick up.
Hello?
Peter?
Peter, listen to me. This is urgent.
Listen to me.
I need 10 million pesos cash, or else!
That's too much, Bea!
I already gave you money.
I already gave you the files.
I did everything you asked me to do!
This is not too much!
The files were useless!
I didn't use them, did I?
So, you listen to me, okay?
This is our new deal.
You give me 10 million pesos cash tomorrow
or our pictures,
your pictures, it will go viral.
So you choose.
You will give me 10 million pesos cash
or bye-bye lawyer,
bye-bye wife, bye-bye family!
Now, you answer me.
What will it be?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Peter, I promise you,
this is the last time, okay?
I swear.
Just give me 10 million pesos.
Then I'm out of your life.
You'll never see me again.
I'll delete all the pictures.
I promise. This is the last time.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[VEHICLES HONKING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come in.
Right there.
Uh, just let me know if you need help
bringing Enrico's things to the hospital.
Thanks.
All right.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENRICO] My big girl is 15 years old now.
Time sure flies, doesn't it?
Happy birthday, my dear.
I heard you're consistently
an honors student.
I'm so proud.
I'm sorry if my only gift
to you is my prayers.
I'll make it up to you next time.
Happy 18th birthday, my dear!
I can't believe you're 18 already.
It's a shame I won't be
your last dance at your debut.
Congratulations, my dear!
I am so proud of you
and your company's success.
I hope LoveList will continue to prosper.
I'm here, cheering you on.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MACHINE BEEPING STEADILY]
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DINO] What do you want?
I know about your plan.
Keep your mouth shut.
Let me join your group.
Your and your mother's passports
and birth certificates are ready.
Oliver will stay there.
As well as Dad.
You're letting your father
live here with us?
[PRECIOUS] Are you sure
about this, Billy?
Still trying to locate
the LoveLine hacker?
This is the only way
I can help Billy.
You know what else
you could do?
Tell Billy your true feelings.
[JORDAN] They've recovered
some of your things.
Would you like to see?
[BEA] I won't let you go to jail.
I've become even more
of a burden to you.
You'll never be a burden to me.
You're the only family I have.
[MARIELA]
You still have a father.
[BILLY] I'm tired of getting my hopes
up for nothing, Auntie.
So I'll put a stop to them myself.
How dare you show up here?!
And you're blaming me
for what happened?
I'm not an idiot!
My father almost died.
That's karma!
[BILLY] Bea!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Get off me!